We last spoke on
video in 2023.
What a memory!
What has changed since then?
In reality, on the one hand, nothing has changed
because the strategy is always the
same and therefore what has changed is
the scale.  At a certain point, as it
continues to grow at a certain
rate, it becomes almost impossible to
ignore.
We met for the first time in
2023. What happened in these 3 years?
From our point of view, as they say
in English, more of the same.
More of the same.
Yes, when you're working with your head down.
What do you think people
won't understand from this IPO?  One thing
I've seen is that many people think this is the end
of the line, right?  Even those who dream of
getting there say "Damn, we'd be there"
done, but for us, a starting point is exciting,
a bit like having
qualified for the World Cup
now.  Exact.  The best is starting now,
so it's beautiful, we're proud, it's not
trivial.
What do you think is the biggest
misconception people out there will
have about this IPO?
It's the fact that from the outside we look like a
financial operation.  We acquire
companies, reshape costs,
increase turnover, but what
we do every day is also
work on our products in order to
significantly improve them.  We demonstrate
that with a few small,
very pissed off teams, with a lot of
responsibility, you can do
a lot and we give a lot of value to
the users of
these products.  Okay.